The daring World War II plot that changed the course of history.
The Eagle Has Landed is a adventure, drama,
action film directed by John Sturges.
When the Nazi high command learns in late 1943 that Winston Churchill will be spending time at a country estate in Norfolk, it
hatches an audacious scheme to kidnap the prime minister and spirit him to Germany for enforced negotiations with Hitler.
Col. Kurt Steiner, played by Michael Caine.
Liam Devlin, played by Donald Sutherland.
Col. Max Radl, played by Robert Duvall.
Molly Prior, played by Jenny Agutter.
Himmler, played by Donald Pleasence.
Admiral Canaris, played by Anthony Quayle.
The Eagle Has Landed is a 1976 British war film directed by John Sturges, and
starring Michael Caine, Donald Sutherland and Robert Duvall.
Based on the 1975 novel The Eagle Has Landed by Jack Higgins, the film is about a fictional
German plot to kidnap Winston Churchill in the middle of the Second World War.
The Eagle Has Landed was Sturges's final film, and
was successful upon its release.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, nazi,
england, world war ii, benito mussolini.
The tone is emotional and intense.